TING
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
EPISODE 27
I'M AN ALIEN
PROFILE
YOSHIKAGE KIRA
KOSAKU KAWAJIRI
KOSAKU
STOMACH MEDICINE
TERRA VENTUS
SHOPPING
CATALOG
THE SHOOTER ROLLS 3 DICE
INTO THE BOWL
THIS WILL RESULT IN WINNING DOUBLE
THE LARGER NUMBER WINS
(HERE, THE 6)
THIS WILL RESULT IN PAYING DOUBLE
THE SHOOTER ROLLS 3 DICE
INTO THE BOWL
EPISODE 28
HIGHWAY GO GO, PART 1